49erswebzone.com 2019-04-14

# 49erswebzone.com Privacy Policy

## Privacy Statement

We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This privacy policy applies to your information that we collect and receive only. We are not responsible for the practices of businesses that we do not own or control nor are we responsible for individuals not employed by us. At no time will we sell your information or release your personally-identifiable data without your permission. You can visit this Site without revealing who you are or providing any personal information about yourself.

By using this Site, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use our services. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, please do not use our sites or services.

This Site contains links to other sites. These include links to resources in related topics and third-party sites that offer other related products. If you visit another website through a link on our site, please consult the privacy policy of the website you are visiting. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites that you may visit.

## Browsing the Site

If you browse through the Site without entering any personal data, we will gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and cannot be linked back to you unless you decide at some point to identify yourself. If you are only browsing, we collect the following information:

  * IP address,
  * The type of browser and operating system used to access our site,
  * The date and time you access our site,
  * The pages you visit (click-through),
  * If you linked to our website from another website, and
  * The address of that website as well as additional information related to your visit.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Site.

## Information Collected

We collect any information that you are willing to volunteer within certain sections of our Site such as our forums. This information is collected during the voluntary registration process. This information may include, but is not limited to, the following:

  * All of the information already specified within the 'Browsing the Site' section,
  * Contact information,
  * Your email address, and
  * Optional information such as, but not limited to, your name, location, birthday, information from social media interactions or website

We may collect the email addresses of consumers who communicate with us or through our authorized vendors via email.

Any information provided by consumers becomes our property once received by us and may be used and disclosed as permitted in this Policy.

We may share your personal information with our affiliated companies in order to identify products or services in which you may have interest, to improve our user experience and generally to engage in market research and for other internal business purposes. We may also aggregate your personal information with others' information and prepare reports on site usage, purchase history or other factors for sale or distribution to others. Those reports are aggregated and include no personally identifying information unless openly volunteered by the user. Finally, we may use your personal information to send you email or postal communications regarding products or services offered by us or by third parties with whom we have relationships in which we think you may be interested. We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown reasons. You may at any time choose not to receive promotional emails from us by replying to any email you receive from us. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to this Site, as well as to facilitate, complete, or confirm any transaction that you may enter into or responding to your inquiry or request.

## Use of Interactive Features

If you choose to transmit, submit or post information through the Site's chat rooms, bulletin boards, other forums (the "Forums"), or other interactive features, we will collect that information you provide. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law and pursuant to our Terms of Use.

## User Generated Content

You may choose to publicly disclose personal information about yourself and others in the course of (i) contributing user generated content (for instance articles, blogs, reviews or podcasts), (ii) communicating with others in our online forums, communities or chat rooms, (iii) creating user profiles for public view, or (iv) posting images, photos or videos. Be aware that information which is voluntarily disclosed in any of these areas of this Site is unencrypted, public information and therefore, there can be no expectation of privacy or confidentiality. Any personal information you submit in the course of interacting in these public activities can be read, collected, or used by other users. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to make public in any of these areas.

## Cookies

We may place "cookies" on your personal computer. "Cookies" are small identifiers sent from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive that help us to recognize you if you visit our website again. Also, our site uses cookies to track how you found our site. Cookies are not designed to be used to get data from your hard drive, your e-mail or any other personal data about you. To protect your privacy, we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings. Please note, however, that if you reject our cookies, it is possible that some web pages may not properly load, your access to certain information might be denied or you might have to enter information about yourself more than once.

## Security

This site has reasonable security measures in place to protect against unauthorized access, disclosure, loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. We cannot assume responsibility or liability for unauthorized access to our servers and systems.

## Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Specifically, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. Google�s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this website and other websites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

In addition, we use clear GIFs or pixel tags to help manage our online advertising. These clear GIFs enable our ad serving company to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site. This allows us to learn which banner ads bring users to our website. The information we collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable.

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as one of our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com.

## Linked Websites and Services

Our sites and services may link to other sites or services operated by affiliates or third parties, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, newsletters, contests or sweepstakes, or applications developed and maintained by third parties. We do not exercise control over third party sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third parties. Once you leave this Site or its services via a link, enable a third-party service, or click an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third-party's site. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices.

We may also provide social media features on our sites and services that enable you to share personal information with your social network(s) and to interact with this Site and its services. Depending on the features, your use of these features may result in the collection or sharing of personal information about you. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and settings on the social media site(s) with which you interact.

## Children's Privacy

This Site and its services are intended for general audiences and are not targeted toward children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, DO NOT disclose or provide any information on this Site or within any of its services.

## Contacting the Web Site

Please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do, we will update this Privacy Policy at our website, so be sure to check back here frequently.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: contact@skybox360.com.

49erswebzone.com - Property of [Skybox 360 Media, LLC](http://www.skybox360.com/)

Last updated September 4, 2013
